(this.webpackJsonpjouzu=this.webpackJsonpjouzu||[]).push([[0],{14:function(e,r,n){},17:function(e,r,n){"use strict";n.r(r);var s=n(1),t=n.n(s),o=n(7),a=n.n(o),i=n(2),c=n(5),u={getQuestions:function(){return c.map((function(e){return{id:e.id,question:e.question}}))||[]},getPossibleAnswers:function(e){var r=c.find((function(r){return r.id===e}));if(r&&r.correct_answer)return{correct:r.correct_answer,incorrect:r.other_answers?r.other_answers:[]}}},d={getRandomInt:function(e,r){return Math.floor(Math.random()*(r-e)+e)}},w=function(e,r,n){for(var s=[],t=0,o=0;o<4;o++)o===e?s.push(r):(s.push(n[t]),t+=1);return s},_={startNewGame:function(){return{questions:u.getQuestions()}},getNextQuestion:function(e){var r=e[d.getRandomInt(0,e.length)],n=u.getPossibleAnswers(r.id),s=function(e,r){r.length<e&&(e=r.length);for(var n=[],s=new Set;s.size<e;){var t=r[d.getRandomInt(0,r.length)];s.has(t)||(n.push(t),s.add(t))}return n}(4,n.incorrect),t=d.getRandomInt(0,4);return{id:r.id,question:r.question,answers:w(t,n.correct,s)}},checkIfCorrectAnswer:function(e,r){return r===u.getPossibleAnswers(e).correct}},l=(n(14),n(15),n(18)),h=n(0),q=function(e){var r=e.className?e.className+" d-grid p-2 ans":"d-grip p-2 ans",n=e.text;return Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:r,children:Object(h.jsx)(l.a,{variant:"outline-dark",className:"display-2",onClick:function(){return e.submitAnswer(n)},active:!0,children:n})})},m=function(e){var r=e.correct?e.correct:0,n=e.incorrect?e.incorrect:0,s=e.resetGame;return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"menu d-flex",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-grow-1 flex-basis-0"}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"d-flex",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-grow-1 px-1",children:Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert alert-success",children:["\u25cb Bien: ",r]})}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-grow-1 px-1",children:Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert alert-danger",children:["\xd7 Mal: ",n]})})]}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"flex-grow-1 d-flex justify-content-end align-items-start flex-basis-0 px-2",children:Object(h.jsx)(l.a,{variant:"outline-dark",onClick:s,active:!0,children:"\u27f2 Reset"})})]})},f=function(e){var r=e.question?e.question:"",n=[{id:1,text:e.ans1?e.ans1:"",className:"ans1"},{id:2,text:e.ans2?e.ans2:"",className:"ans2"},{id:3,text:e.ans3?e.ans3:"",className:"ans3"},{id:4,text:e.ans4?e.ans4:"",className:"ans4"}],s=e.correct,t=e.incorrect,o=e.submitAnswer,a=e.resetGame;return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"interface",children:[Object(h.jsx)(m,{correct:s,incorrect:t,resetGame:a}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:r}),n.map((function(e){return Object(h.jsx)(q,{text:e.text,className:e.className,submitAnswer:o},e.id)}))]})},b=function(){var e=Object(s.useRef)({}),r=Object(s.useState)(0),n=Object(i.a)(r,2),t=n[0],o=n[1],a=Object(s.useState)(0),c=Object(i.a)(a,2),u=c[0],d=c[1],w=Object(s.useState)(""),l=Object(i.a)(w,2),q=l[0],m=l[1],b=Object(s.useState)(""),v=Object(i.a)(b,2),j=v[0],g=v[1],p=Object(s.useState)(""),O=Object(i.a)(p,2),x=O[0],C=O[1],N=Object(s.useState)(""),P=Object(i.a)(N,2),S=P[0],A=P[1],E=Object(s.useState)(""),k=Object(i.a)(E,2),L=k[0],I=k[1],T=Object(s.useState)(""),R=Object(i.a)(T,2),y=R[0],G=R[1],M=function(){var r=_.getNextQuestion(e.current.questions);m(r.id),g(r.question),C(r.answers[0]),A(r.answers[1]),I(r.answers[2]),G(r.answers[3])};return Object(s.useEffect)((function(){e.current=_.startNewGame(),M()}),[]),Object(h.jsx)(f,{correct:t,incorrect:u,question:j,ans1:x,ans2:S,ans3:L,ans4:y,submitAnswer:function(e){_.checkIfCorrectAnswer(q,e)?o(t+1):d(u+1),M()},resetGame:function(){o(0),d(0)}})},v=Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));function j(e,r){navigator.serviceWorker.register(e).then((function(e){e.onupdatefound=function(){var n=e.installing;null!=n&&(n.onstatechange=function(){"installed"===n.state&&(navigator.serviceWorker.controller?(console.log("New content is available and will be used when all tabs for this page are closed. See https://cra.link/PWA."),r&&r.onUpdate&&r.onUpdate(e)):(console.log("Content is cached for offline use."),r&&r.onSuccess&&r.onSuccess(e)))})}})).catch((function(e){console.error("Error during service worker registration:",e)}))}var g=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,19)).then((function(r){var n=r.getCLS,s=r.getFID,t=r.getFCP,o=r.getLCP,a=r.getTTFB;n(e),s(e),t(e),o(e),a(e)}))};a.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(t.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)(b,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),function(e){if("serviceWorker"in navigator){if(new URL("/n4vocabulario",window.location.href).origin!==window.location.origin)return;window.addEventListener("load",(function(){var r="".concat("/n4vocabulario","/service-worker.js");v?(!function(e,r){fetch(e,{headers:{"Service-Worker":"script"}}).then((function(n){var s=n.headers.get("content-type");404===n.status||null!=s&&-1===s.indexOf("javascript")?navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister().then((function(){window.location.reload()}))})):j(e,r)})).catch((function(){console.log("No internet connection found. App is running in offline mode.")}))}(r,e),navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(){console.log("This web app is being served cache-first by a service worker. To learn more, visit https://cra.link/PWA")}))):j(r,e)}))}}(),g()},5:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"id":"0","question":"\u3042\u3058","correct_answer":"Sabor/Gusto","other_answers":["Pie"]},{"id":"1","question":"\u3042\u304b\u3093\u307c\u3046","correct_answer":"Bebe","other_answers":["Calefector"]},{"id":"2","question":"\u3042\u3093\u306a\u3044","correct_answer":"Guiar","other_answers":["Paz mental"]},{"id":"3","question":"\u3042\u3093\u3057\u3093","correct_answer":"Paz mental/ Alivio","other_answers":["Guiar"]},{"id":"4","question":"\u3042\u3093\u305c\u3093","correct_answer":"Seguro, seguridad","other_answers":["Alivio"]},{"id":"5","question":"\u3070\u3042\u3044","correct_answer":"Caso, situacion, circunstancia","other_answers":["Seguro, seguridad"]},{"id":"6","question":"\u3079\u3064","correct_answer":"Aparte, por separado","other_answers":["Importante"]},{"id":"7","question":"\u307c\u3046\u3048\u304d","correct_answer":"Comercio","other_answers":["Literatura"]},{"id":"8","question":"\u3076\u3093\u304c\u304f","correct_answer":"Literatura","other_answers":["Comercio"]},{"id":"9","question":"\u3076\u3093\u304b","correct_answer":"Cultura, civilizacion","other_answers":["Literatura"]},{"id":"10","question":"\u3076\u3093\u307d\u3046","correct_answer":"Gramatica","other_answers":["Literatura"]},{"id":"11","question":"\u3061","correct_answer":"Sangre","other_answers":["Sabor/Gusto"]},{"id":"12","question":"\u3061\u304b\u3089","correct_answer":"Poder","other_answers":["Cuerpo"]},{"id":"13","question":"\u3061\u308a","correct_answer":"Geografia","other_answers":["Literatura"]},{"id":"14","question":"\u3061\u3085\u3046\u3044","correct_answer":"Tener cuidado","other_answers":["Hospedaje"]},{"id":"15","question":"\u6ce8\u5c04\u3000\u3061\u3085\u3046\u3057\u3083","correct_answer":"Inyeccion","other_answers":["Estacionamiento"]},{"id":"16","question":"\u99d0\u8eca\u3000\u3061\u3085\u3046\u3057\u3083","correct_answer":"Estacionamiento","other_answers":["Inyeccion"]},{"id":"17","question":"\u3060\u3044\u305f\u3044","correct_answer":"Aproximadamente, mas o menos","other_answers":["Calefactor"]},{"id":"18","question":"\u3060\u3093\u307c\u3046","correct_answer":"Calefactor","other_answers":["Genero Masculino"]},{"id":"19","question":"\u3060\u3093\u305b\u3044","correct_answer":"Genero Masculino","other_answers":["Comercio"]},{"id":"20","question":"\u3052\u3057\u3085\u304f","correct_answer":"Hospedaje","other_answers":["Condicion"]},{"id":"21","question":"\u304e\u3058\u3085\u3064","correct_answer":"Gadgets, habilidad tecnica","other_answers":["Traduccion"]},{"id":"22","question":"\u3050\u3042\u3044","correct_answer":"Condicion, estado fisico de alguien","other_answers":["Observar"]},{"id":"23","question":"\u306f\u3044\u3051\u3093","correct_answer":"Observar (Muy formal)","other_answers":["Lo contrario"]},{"id":"24","question":"\u306f\u3093\u305f\u3044","correct_answer":"Lo contrario","other_answers":["Observar"]},{"id":"25","question":"\u306f\u3064\u304a\u3093","correct_answer":"Pronunciacion","other_answers":["Lo contrario"]},{"id":"26","question":"\u306f\u3084\u3057","correct_answer":"Bosque","other_answers":["Respuesta"]},{"id":"27","question":"\u3078\u3093\u3058","correct_answer":"Respuesta","other_answers":["Observar"]},{"id":"28","question":"\u3072\u304d\u3060\u3057","correct_answer":"Tirar y sacar","other_answers":["Salir"]},{"id":"29","question":"\u3072\u3053\u3046","correct_answer":"Vuelo","other_answers":["Lista"]},{"id":"30","question":"\u3072\u308b\u307e","correct_answer":"Durante el dia, momento del dia","other_answers":["Descanso del mediodia"]},{"id":"31","question":"\u3072\u3064\u3088\u3046","correct_answer":"Necesario","other_answers":["Respuesta"]},{"id":"32","question":"\u307b\u3093\u3084\u304f","correct_answer":"Traduccion","other_answers":["Libreria"]},{"id":"33","question":"\u307b\u3046\u308a\u3064","correct_answer":"Transmision","other_answers":["Observar"]},{"id":"34","question":"\u3073\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Lista","other_answers":["Transmision"]},{"id":"35","question":"\u3044\u304c\u3044","correct_answer":"A excepcion","other_answers":["No menos de..."]},{"id":"36","question":"\u3044\u304c\u304f","correct_answer":"Medicina","other_answers":["Enfermeria"]},{"id":"37","question":"\u3044\u3058\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"No menos de...","other_answers":["A excepcion"]},{"id":"38","question":"\u3058\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Soltera","other_answers":["Jovencita"]},{"id":"39","question":"\u3058\u3087\u305b\u3044","correct_answer":"Mujer joven, jovencita","other_answers":["Soltera"]},{"id":"40","question":"\u3058\u3085\u3093\u3073","correct_answer":"Planificar","other_answers":["Direccion"]},{"id":"41","question":"\u3058\u3085\u3046\u3057\u3087","correct_answer":"Direccion","other_answers":["Planificar"]},{"id":"42","question":"\u304b\u3079","correct_answer":"Pared","other_answers":["Planificar"]},{"id":"43","question":"\u304b\u304c\u304f","correct_answer":"Ciencia","other_answers":["Transmision"]},{"id":"44","question":"\u304b\u304c\u307f","correct_answer":"Espejo","other_answers":["Ciencia"]},{"id":"45","question":"\u304b\u3044","correct_answer":"Conjunto, reunion","other_answers":["Vuelta"]},{"id":"46","question":"\u304b\u3044\u3058\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Lugar de reunion","other_answers":["Conjunto, reunion"]},{"id":"47","question":"\u304b\u3044\u308f","correct_answer":"Conversacion","other_answers":["Ciencia"]},{"id":"48","question":"\u304b\u3058","correct_answer":"Incendio","other_answers":["Picante"]},{"id":"49","question":"\u304b\u306a\u3044","correct_answer":"Esposa","other_answers":["Incendio"]},{"id":"50","question":"\u304b\u306d\u3082\u3061","correct_answer":"Rico","other_answers":["Relacion"]},{"id":"51","question":"\u304b\u3093\u3054","correct_answer":"Enfermeria","other_answers":["De forma"]},{"id":"52","question":"\u304b\u308f\u308a","correct_answer":"Reemplazo","other_answers":["Telegrama"]},{"id":"53","question":"\u3067\u3093\u3068\u3046","correct_answer":"Luz Electrica","other_answers":["Utencilios"]},{"id":"54","question":"\u3069\u3046\u3050","correct_answer":"Utencilios","other_answers":["Telegrama"]},{"id":"55","question":"\u3048\u3060","correct_answer":"Rama","other_answers":["Luz Electrica"]},{"id":"56","question":"\u3048\u3093\u308a\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Modestia","other_answers":["Consulta"]},{"id":"57","question":"\u3075\u3079\u3093","correct_answer":"Inconveniente","other_answers":["Modestia"]},{"id":"58","question":"\u3075\u304f\u3057\u3085\u3046","correct_answer":"Repaso","other_answers":["Inconveniente"]},{"id":"59","question":"\u3075\u304f\u3055\u3064","correct_answer":"Intrincado/Complicado","other_answers":["Repaso"]},{"id":"60","question":"\u3075\u3064\u3046","correct_answer":"Comun","other_answers":["Complicado"]},{"id":"61","question":"\u3052\u3093\u3044\u3093","correct_answer":"Origen","other_answers":["Complicado"]},{"id":"62","question":"\u3053\u3046\u3069\u3046","correct_answer":"Auditorio","other_answers":["Origen"]},{"id":"63","question":"\u3053\u3046\u304c\u3044","correct_answer":"Suburbio","other_answers":["Origen"]},{"id":"64","question":"\u3053\u3046\u304e","correct_answer":"Discurso","other_answers":["Suburbio"]},{"id":"65","question":"\u3053\u3046\u304e\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Industria","other_answers":["Fabrica"]},{"id":"66","question":"\u3053\u3046\u3058\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Fabrica","other_answers":["Complicado"]},{"id":"67","question":"\u3044\u304b","correct_answer":"Menos","other_answers":["Al menos"]},{"id":"68","question":"\u3044\u306a\u3044","correct_answer":"Al menos","other_answers":["Menos"]},{"id":"69","question":"\u3044\u306a\u304b","correct_answer":"Lugar de origen/area rural","other_answers":["Al menos"]},{"id":"70","question":"\u3044\u3063\u3058\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Toda la vida","other_answers":["Menos"]},{"id":"71","question":"\u3044\u3068","correct_answer":"Hilo","other_answers":["Piedra"]},{"id":"72","question":"\u3044\u308f\u3044","correct_answer":"Celebracion","other_answers":["Hilo"]},{"id":"73","question":"\u3058\u3060\u3044","correct_answer":"Epoca","other_answers":["Celebracion"]},{"id":"74","question":"\u3058\u3053","correct_answer":"Accidente","other_answers":["Epoca"]},{"id":"74","question":"\u3058\u3080","correct_answer":"Administracion","other_answers":["Epoca"]},{"id":"75","question":"\u3058\u3093\u3053\u3046","correct_answer":"Poblacion","other_answers":["Semaforo"]},{"id":"76","question":"\u3058\u3057\u3093","correct_answer":"Terremoto","other_answers":["Poblacion"]},{"id":"77","question":"\u3058\u3066\u3093","correct_answer":"Enciclopedia","other_answers":["Terremoto"]},{"id":"78","question":"\u306d\u307c\u3046","correct_answer":"Quedarse dormido","other_answers":["Hilo"]},{"id":"79","question":"\u306b\u3093\u304e\u3087\u3046","correct_answer":"Mu\xf1eca","other_answers":["Complicado"]},{"id":"80","question":"\u306e\u308a\u3082\u306e","correct_answer":"Transporte/Vehiculo","other_answers":["Combinar"]},{"id":"81","question":"\u306b\u3085\u3046\u304c\u304f","correct_answer":"Ingresante","other_answers":["Secundaria"]},{"id":"83","question":"\u3051","correct_answer":"Pelaje","other_answers":["Pelo"]},{"id":"84","question":"\u3051\u3044\u304b\u304f","correct_answer":"Plan/Proyecto","other_answers":["Asistir"]},{"id":"85","question":"\u3051\u3044\u3051\u3093","correct_answer":"Experiencia","other_answers":["Plan/Proyecto"]},{"id":"86","question":"\u3051\u3044\u3055\u3064","correct_answer":"Policia","other_answers":["Experiencia"]},{"id":"87","question":"\u3051\u3044\u3056\u3044","correct_answer":"Economia","other_answers":["Experiencia"]},{"id":"88","question":"\u3051\u3093\u3076\u3064","correct_answer":"Observar","other_answers":["Proyecto"]},{"id":"89","question":"\u307f\u3082\u306e","correct_answer":"Atraccion/ Espectaculo","other_answers":["Observar"]},{"id":"90","question":"\u3051\u3093\u3076\u3064","correct_answer":"Turistear","other_answers":["Proyecto"]}]')}},[[17,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.b97fd190.chunk.js.map